Guide to the Committee on the Protection of Human Subjects, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records, circa 1967-1983; Accession 1988-A-083
  - Reiss: Social Science Training, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 238)
  - Yee: Problem-Solving Styles of Social Comparison and Autonomous Achievement Motivated Children, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 239)
  - Sherrod: Infants' Early Social Perceptions, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 240)
  - Kessen: Child Psychology Research Training (lacking), 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 241)
  - Wolf: The Effects of Visibility and Gender in Dyadic Interaction, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 242)
  - Bell: Comparative Sociology Training Program, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 243)
  - Lamb: The relationship between the infant and his father and mother: The growth of social attachments in infancy, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 245)
  - Collins: Attributes in relation to memory for the infant, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 246)
  - Birchette: A Developmental Study of Cognitive Abilities in Human and Nonhuman Primates, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 247)
  - Child: "Human performance on computerized random mazes", 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 248)
  - Abelson (Hornbeck): Inference and Memory Structures in Understanding, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 249)
  - Garner: Perception of Structure (lacking), 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 250)
  - Goldin: Responses to situation involving persuasive communications, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 251)
  - Hargis: A Long-Term Weight Control Program, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 252)
  - Wandersman: Effects of Mothers' Presence on Children's Expression of Cognitive Abilities under Standard and Optimizing Conditions: A Social Class Comparison, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 253)
  - Witte: Democracy, Authority, and Alienation in Work, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 254)
  - Ellsworth: The Role of the Face in the Experience of Emotion., 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 255)
  - Jose: Specificity of eye contact avoidance in autistic, retarded and normal children, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 256)
  - Achenbach: ChiId Behavior Suwey, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 257)
  - Zigler: Long Term Effects of Head Start., 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 258)
  - Fetter: An Integrated Clinical Management System for the Obstetrical Patient, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 259)
  - Reppucci: Social Identity of Behavior Modification, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 260)
  - Turner: The Development of Explicit Linguistic Segmentation in Children, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 261)
  - Hamilton: Influence on Interracial Perception and Interaction, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 262)
  - Herrera: Variations in Personality Attributes of Social and Solitary, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 263)
  - Stipek: School and the Development of Attitudes in First Graders, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 264)
  - Myers: A Prospective Community Study of Depressive Symptoms, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 266)
  - Mullins: Alienation of Convalescent Home Residents: The Effects of lntra-Organizational Stratification, Peer Relations, and Familial Relations, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 267)
  - Rothbaum: Imitation of Parents and Strange Adults on Objective and Subjective Judgements, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 268)
  - Slaby: Help-Seeking Behavior in White Male College Students, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 269)
  - Lamb and Zigler: The Components of Delay of Gratification, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 270)
  - Sternberg: The Componential Analysis of Human Intel ligence, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 271)
  - Kessen: Stimulus Sensitivity of Obese-tending Infants, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 272)
  - Bell: Training Program in Comparative Sociology, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 273)
  - Riedel: Pilot Study of the Role of the New Health Practitioner, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 274)
  - Fallot: The Psychological Work of Reminiscing in Late Adulthood, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 275)
  - Myers: Social Science Research Training: Training in Sociology and Community Mental Health, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 276)
  - Nelson and Wilbur: Formation of the Concept of Magnetic Polarity by Young Children, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 277)
  - Kessen: Child Psychology Research Training, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 278)
  - Truman: Ego Development and Level of Object Representations in Dreams, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 279)
  - Singer: Clinical Psychology Training Grant, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 280)
  - Tourangeau: The Relations of Actions to Behaviors, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 281)
  - Katz: Changing Beliefs Concerning Desirability: A Mediating Process Analysis, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 282)
  - Preston: Adaptations of Registered Nurses to Manifest Human Abnormality and Ambiguity within an Institutional Context, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 283)
  - Jose: Familiarization to a Novel Person by Autistic, Behaviorally Disturbed and Normal Child, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 284)
  - Janis and Abelson: Program in Personality and Social Psychology, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 285)
  - Reiss, Jr.: Social Science Research Training, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 286)
  - Singer: TV Viewing and Imaginative Development: A Longitudinal and Parent Intervention Study, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 287)
  - Weinberg: Information Processing in Policy/Program Evaluation, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 288)
  - Ward: Political Ideology: An Intergenerational Re-Study, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 289)
  - Hochschild: Public Attitudes Toward the Redistribution of Wealth, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 290)
  - Gruber: Democratic Control and the Administrative State, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 291)
  - Billington: The influence of visual responses to valenced self disclosure on social perception, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 292)
  - Kubovy: Grouping Processes in Auditory Perception, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 293)
  - Weitz: Social and psychological correlates of membership in consciousness raising groups and in a women's technical self help group, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 294)
  - Perlmutter: Structure and Processing of Human Long-term Memory, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 295)
  - Reder: Prose Comprehension: Experimentation and Computer Simulation, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 296)
  - Bockelman and Ross: Biomedical Research Support Program, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 297)
  - Singer: Changes in Patient-Expectancy as a Factor in Continuance in Psychotherapy, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 298)
  - Garner (lacking): Perception of Structure, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 299)
  - Blechner: Hemispheric specialization, selective attention, and information integration for speech and nonspeech, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 300)
  - Anderson: Computer Simulation of Language Acquisition, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 301)
  - Crowder: The Processing of Speech in Human Short-Term Memory (lacking), 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 302)
  - Nelson: Conceptual Development in Early Childhood, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 303)
  - Toffler: The Role Making Process of the Physician's Assistant, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 304)
  - Shin: Variation of Hospital Cost and Product Heterogeneity, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 305)
  - Zigler: Immidiate and Long-Term Effects of Head Start, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 306)
  - Hoyt: A Study of Beliefs and Fantasies Regarding Parental Sexuality, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 307)
  - Searle: Training of Foreign-Educated House Staff, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 308)
  - McDonald: Random Sampling of Ongoing Thought Processes, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 309)
  - Robertson: Day care and children's attitudes toward adults, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 310)
  - Fowler: Children's understanding of color, number, and length in picture recognition and card-sorting tasks, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 311)
  - Scott: Auditory perception in Human Infant, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 313)
  - Kaye: A Developmental Study of the Child's Understanding of time and place, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 314)
  - Baldrich: The State and Class Alliances, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 315)
  - Feshbach: Cognitive and Affective Specialization of the Cerebral Hemispheres, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 316)
  - Lustman: Imitation in Noninstitutionalized and Institutionalized Retarded Children - Imitation of Adults, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 317)
  - Kubovy: Organization in Auditory Perception Memory for, and processing of, linguistic material, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 318)
  - Anderson: Memory for, and processing of, linguistic material, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 319)
  - Berndt: Children's understanding of reciprocity norms, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 320)
  - Wilbur: A Comparison of Linguistic and Functional Information in Comcpet Learning by Young Children, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 321)
  - Rosenbaum: Urban Employees' Adaptation to Opportunity, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 322)
  - Alderfer: Management Training and Group Mobility on The Job, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 323)
  - Rodin: Perceived Control and Crowding Stress, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 324)
  - Rodin: External Responsiveness, Human Feeding and Obesity, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 325)
  - Turner: The Development of the Understanding of Logical Connectives, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 326)
  - Fowler: A Visual Rehearsal Strategy for ChiIdren's Short-term Memory, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 327)
  - Sternberg: The Development of Inductive reasoning Process, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 328)
  - Greundel: Episodic Encoding: A Study of Preschool Children's Representation of Events, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 329)
  - Anderson: A Computer Simulation Model of Language Processing and Reading Skills, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 330)
  - Myers: A Prospective Community Study of Depressive Symptoms, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 331)
  - Berndt: Children's Notions of Friendship and its Behavioral Consequences, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 332)
  - Frye: Memory for Hidden Objects, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 333)
  - Berndt: The Development of Reciprocity, Equity and in-group Norms, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 334)
  - Kubovy: Process Models of Probabilistic Categorization Decisions, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 335)
  - Anderson: A Model for Procedural Learning, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 336)
  - Crowder: The Processing of Speech in Human Short-Term Memory, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 337)
  - Schwartz: Psychophysiology of Facial Expression and Emotion, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 338)
  - Milstein-Kessen: Temporal Aspects of Visual Perception in the Very Young Infant, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 339)
  - Hoffman: Effects of Press Publicity on Criminal Proceedings, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 340)
  - Powell: Genetics of Natural Populations, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 341)
  - Klos: The Assessment of Autonomy Competence, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 342)
  - Myers: Social Science Research Training: Training in Sociology and Community Mental Health, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 343)
  - Waters: The Social Organization of Petty Commodity Production, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 344)
  - Levy: Enamel Model Modification Affecting Protein Adhesion, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 345)
  - Kessen-Nelson: Graduate Research Training in Developmental Psychology, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 346)
  - Nelson: Development of Script Knowledge by Young Children, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 347)
  - Rosegrant: Esthetic Preference and Possibility Related Experiences, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 348)
  - Singer: Clinical Psychology Training Grant, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 349)
  - Klos: The Assessment of Autonomy Competence, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 350)
  - Reiss, Jr.: Social Science Research Training: Sociology of Social Control, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 351)
  - Cacioppo: Voluntary control of heart rate in times of stress, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 352)
  - Berndt: The Influence of Friends, Classmates, and Parents on Children, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 353)
  - Abelson-Janis (lacking): Behavioral Expectancies of Professionals Towards Labeled Children, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 354)
  - Myers: A Prospective Community Study of Depressive Symptoms, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 355)
  - Phillips-DeMott: Developmental and Experiential Determinants of Self-image Disparity in Young Children, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 356)
  - Coleman: Students' Conceptualizations of Competitior in The Classroom, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 357)
  - Heilman: The Social Nature of Concerns about Freedom, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 358)
  - Engleman: Organization of Cholesteryl Esters in Atherosclerosis, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 359)
  - Garner: Perception of Structure, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 360)
  - Berndt: Effects of Friendship on Social and Moral Development, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 361)
  - Nowaczyk: Changes in Semantic Context During an STM Task, 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 362)
  - Watson: Assessment of Solitary and Group Training in Role Playing, 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 363)
  - Herbert: Adult Psychosocial Developmental Periods in Black Entrepreneurs and Blue Collar Workers, 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 364)
  - Subrata Saha: Mechanical Properties of Hard Tissue: Evaluation and Mathematical Modeling, 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 365)
  - Miles: Work Stress: Causes, Consequences and Management, 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 366)
  - Berndt: Children's Notions of Friendship and and their reaction to unfriendly behavior by friends, 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 367)
  - Trickett: Continuity and the timing of intervention: An Evaluation Study, 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 368)
  - Sherrod: Infants' Perception of Faces, 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 369)
  - Trickett: Career Development in New Haven's Headstart Program, 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 370)
  - Wright: Modernization and Popular Literature in Malaysia, 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 371)
  - Lehnert: A Computerized Interview System for Post Myocardial Infarction Patients, 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 372)
  - Saha: A New Method to Measure the Rate of Fracture Healing, 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 373)
  - Bassett: A study of the effects of task goal and schedule choice on productivity, 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 374)
  - Saha: Improved Properties of Reinforced Bone Cement, 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 375)
  - Engleman: Cholesteryl Esters in Membranes and Atherosclerosis, 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 376)
  - Rabkin: ANA: Native American revitalization in Upstate New York, 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 377)
  - Nelson: Conceptual and Semantic Development in Children, 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 378)
  - Reder: Prose Comprehension: Experimentation and Computer Stimulation, 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 379)
  - Zigler: Cognition and Motivation in Retarded Individuals, 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 380)
  - Jose: Sociolinguistic variables in adult - child conversations, 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 381)
  - Components of Individual Differences In Human Intelligence, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 382)
  - American Attitudes and Behavioral Relations to Wildlife and Natural Habitats, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 383)
  - Cognition and Motivation in Retarded Individuals, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 384)
  - Relative Deprivation and Working Women, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 385)
  - A Developmental Investigation of Receptive Language, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 386)
  - Strategies of Story Comprehension, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 387)
  - The Effect of Language Formality and Experimenter Status on Student Task Performance, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 388)
  - Children's Memory for Temporally Sequenced Events, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 389)
  - Cognitive Factors in Improvisational Role-Playing, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 390)
  - Work and the Transition to Fatherhood, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 391)
  - Clinical Psychology Training Grant, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 392)
  - Temporal Aspects of Visual Perception in the Very Young Infant, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 393)
  - Enhanced Fluoride Penetration and Retention in Enamel, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 394)
  - Some Caries Relationships Examined Epidemiologically, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 395)
  - Effect of Status and Sex on Felt Gratifications, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 396)
  - Sex Differences in Language, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 397)
  - Friendship: Developments in Conceptions and Behavior, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 398)
  - Graduate Research Training in Developmental Psychology, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 399)
  - Ethnic Identity in Portuguese-American Adolescents, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 400)
  - Berndt: Reciprocity Norms and Reciprocal Behavior in Preschool Children, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 401)
  - Sternberg: The Development of Human Reasoning, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 402)
  - Myers: Social Science Research Training: Training in Sociology and Community Mental Health, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 403)
  - Reiss: Social Science Research Training: Sociology of Social Control, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 404)
  - Ogawa: A Literary Biography of Akutagawa Ryunosuke, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 405)
  - Thypin: From Moradores to Boias Prias: Political Consequences of Changing Relations of Production in Rural Northeast Brazil, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 406)
  - Pittman: The Agrarian Roots of Rebellion and Its Frustration: The Plantation Economy of Mexico and Peru (1880--1920), 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 407)
  - Joseph: Wolof Oral Praise Poetry in the Former African Kingdom of Kayor, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 408)
  - Putterman: Economic Decision-Making of the Tanzanian Peasant: Collective and Individual Production, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 409)
  - Kuipers: Speech and Society in an Indonesian Community: Ritual Language in West Sumba, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 410)
  - Conagham: The New Alliance: Multinational Corporations, the State and the National Bourgeoisie in Ecuador, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 411)
  - Scott: The Study of Post-Peasant Society in Rural Malaysia, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 412)
  - Hartka: Attitudes Toward Women and Rape, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 413)
  - Schustack: Production and Recognition in Early Language, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 414)
  - Brett-Smith: Bogolanfini: A Mud-Dyed Cloth from Mali, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 415)
  - Jeffries: Africanisms in Contemporary Afro-American Painting, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 416)
  - Lepper: Analysis of Clinical Case Histories, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 417)
  - Lepper: Utilizing Experimental Research Findings, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 418)
  - Myers: Mental Health (Services) Evaluation Training Program, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 419)
  - Warrenberg: Behavioral Etiology and Treatment of Hypertension, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 420)
  - Healy: Short-term Memory for Order Information, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 421)
  - Metcalf: The Role of Non-Facial Muscular Activity on the Experience of Emotion, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 422)
  - Garner: Perception of Structure, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 423)
  - Feldman: Influences on Phonological Recoding During Reading, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 425)
  - McCartney: Narrative Reconstruction in Children, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 426)
  - Dowler: University Records Survey, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 427)
  - Chevron: Trans-situational adaptive behavior as a function of sex-role orientation and cognitive style, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 428)
  - Burch: Coastal Wetlands: A case Study of the Social Conditions Associated with Conservation and Regulatory Effectiveness., 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 429)
  - Dannefer: Leisure and Well-being: a Longitudinal Study, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 430)
  - Healy: Process Models of Probabilistic Categorization Decisions, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 431)
  - Crowder: The Processing of Speech in Human Short-Term Memory, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 432)
  - Tuteur: Automatic Interpretation of Electroencephalograms, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 433)
  - Kurash: The Transition from High School to College: A Study of Separation Patterns in Late Adolescence, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 434)
  - Levy-Warren: Transcultural Movement, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 435)
  - Cohn: Control and the elderly: Social-physical implications, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 436)
  - Berndt: Reciprocity Norms, Friendship Conceptions, and Behavior in Preschoolers, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 437)
  - Janis-Abelson: Program in Personality and Social Psychohgy, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 438)
  - Washington: The Influence of Age, Setting, Condition and Humor Stimulus Features on the Humor Responses of Children, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 439)
  - Seitz: Immediate and Long-Term Effects of Head Start, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 440)
  - Scarr: Barriers in women's Educational Equity: A Longitudinal Family Study, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 441)
  - Kristeller: Rest, Relaxation and Self-control of Eating Behavior in the Treatment of Hypertension, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 442)
  - Fetter: A Casemix Approach to the Integration of PSRO, Rate Setting and Planning Functions for Acute Care Hospitals, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 443)
  - Saha: Repair of Osteocarcoma Defects and Related Fractures, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 444)
  - Rosenbaum: Urban Employee's Adaptation to Opportunity, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 445)
  - Sternberg: Components of Individual Differences in Human Intelligence, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 446)
  - McGuire: Content, Structure and Functioning of Belief Systems, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 447)
  - Kubovy: Attention and Pre-Attention in Audition and Vision, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 448)
  - Healy: The size and the acquisition of reading units, 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 449)
  - Berndt: Friendships: Developmental Changes and Correlates, 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 450)
  - McGuire: Historical changes in the prevalence of left handedness, 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 451)
  - Machlowitz: Determining the Effects of Workaholism, 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 452)
  - Bloom-Feshbach: Separation Responses and Nursery School Adjustment, 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 453)
  - Myers: The Epidemiology Catchment Area Program, 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 454)
  - Billington: The influence of a unionization effort on workers' sense of political efficacy, personal control, and job satisfaction, 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 455)
  - Singer and Newman: Stimulating Cognitive and Imaginative Development in Preschool-Aged Children Through the Use of Specially prepared Materials and Parent Education, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 456)
  - Berndt: Friendships in Middle Childhood, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 457)
  - Zuckerman-Singer: Teaching Elementary School Children to Use Television Effectively, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 458)
  - Gonzalez: Casual reasoning in judgments under uncertainty: a reexamination, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 459)
  - Healy: Learning Language Rules, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 460)
  - Wall: Linear and Spatial Representation in Memory, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 461)
  - Leaf: Mental Health Research Training Program, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 462)
  - Roseman: Perception of Biographical Events, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 463)
  - Levi: Chance Events, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 464)
  - Singer: Clinical-Community Psychology Training Program, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 465)
  - Berman: Coping with Interpersonal Loss: Adjustment in Divorced and Widowed Woman, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 466)
  - Scarr: Graduate Research Training in Child Psychology, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 467)
  - Walker: An Experimental Investigation of Non-decisionmaking, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 468)
  - Pospisil: Acculturation, Urbanization, and Law, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 469)
  - London: The effects of attentional vs. directional instructions in biofeedback control of heart rate, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 470)
  - Singer: Clinical-Community Psychology Training Program, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 471)
  - Kessen: Temporal Aspects of Visual Perception in the Very Young Infant, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 472)
  - Furrow: Social and Asocial Speech in Language-Learning Children, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 473)
  - Veilleux: Self-Image Disparity as a Function of Premorbid Social Competence and Psychiatric Diagnosis, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 474)
  - Klos: The Effects of Confrontation Style and Outcome on Subsequent Thought: A Simulation of Parent-Adolescent Interaction, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 475)
  - Cascione: Development of Adaptive Behavior in Retarded Persons, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 476)